Foster Brothers
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Foster Brothers records
1875-1973 (bulk 1893-1942)
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Foster Brothers
12.5 linear feet
The records of Boston picture frame company Foster Brothers measure 12.5 linear feet and date from 1875-1973 with the bulk of the material falling between 1893 and 1942. Correspondence, stock records, financial records, writings, miscellaneous business records, printed material, scrapbooks, and photographs document the history of this company that operated a factory, retail store, and wholesale and mail order businesses between 1893 and 1942. A small number of family papers are included, with items pre-dating and post-dating the business.
Provenance
Helen Foster Osborne, daughter of John R. Foster, donated the Foster Brothers records to the Archives in four installments between 1973 and 1976.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment.
Historical Note
Established by Stephen Bartlett Foster (1856-1932) and John Roy Foster (1863-1931), Foster Brothers opened in 1893 at 164 Boylston Street, Boston. By 1896, Foster Brothers had moved to 3 Park Square, just around the corner from its first location. Eventually, the business relocated to 4 Park Square, where it stayed for the remainder of its existence. The original Foster Brothers factory was housed in the old Parkman’s Market building on Cambridge Street in Boston. In 1918, the Fosters built a new factory in Arlington, the suburb in which the brothers lived.
Foster Brothers was known for high quality frames that featured expert carving and gilding by fine craftsmen, consistent with the esthetic and philosophy of the Arts and Crafts movement of the time. Their frames that incorporated elements of early Dutch frames especially appealed to Boston School artists such as Edmund Tarbell and William MacGregor Paxton. Custom orders were welcomed from museums, galleries, collectors, and artists. In the 1890s, Foster Brothers operated a small gallery that featured watercolors and sketches by local artists; sporadic exhibitions continued throughout the 1930s. Early business cards and advertisements indicate that the company sold "wedding presents, etchings, engravings, water colors and picture frames." Among its best selling merchandise were mirrors in a wide variety of styles. As early as 1898, Foster Brothers began to copyright and publish reproductions of paintings, drawings, silhouettes, and miniatures. These were framed in sets and sold by Foster Brothers in its retail shop and by mail order; in addition, they were distributed through department stores, furniture stores, gift shops, and interior decorators.
John Roy Foster was in charge of promotion and merchandising, designing the retail line, and managing the company’s wholesale and mail order businesses. Stephen Bartlett Foster managed the factory and oversaw all aspects of the manufacturing. Helen J. Foster, John’s daughter, studied art at Smith College and by the late 1920s was a successful manager and saleswoman in the retail store. The Depression brought a sharp decline in sales. After the deaths of John and Stephen Foster, Helen and her husband, Shattuck Osborne, owned and managed Foster Brothers for another decade. Although the business closed in 1942, Foster Brothers frames continue to command high prices and are highly prized and sought after today.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Boston picture frame company Foster Brothers measure 12.5 linear feet and date from 1875 to 1973 with the bulk of the material falling between 1893 and 1942. Correspondence, stock records, financial records, writings, miscellaneous business records, printed material, scrapbooks, and photographs document the history of the picture frame company that operated a factory, retail store, and wholesale and mail order businesses between 1893 and 1942. A small number of family papers are included, including items from periods when Foster Brothers was not in business. Scattered throughout the collection are small slips of papers with explanatory notes and background information supplied by the donor, Helen Foster Osborne.
Correspondence mostly concerns routine business with suppliers, distributors, and wholesale and retail customers and is relatively sparse for 1897-1941. Foster Brothers’ last year in business, 1942, is well documented and includes letters from S. W. Osborne (Margaret Foster’s husband) written while traveling to meet with wholesale clients in cities throughout the Northeast and Midwest.
Stock records include stock cards, inventory records and price lists. Also found are a large number of paper stencils that were used to transfer carving designs to frames, and extensive drawings of frames and moldings including finished, colored drawings by master craftsman C. F. Richter.
Financial records consist mainly of routine accounting records, but also include annual financial reports, orders, and sales records. Among the writings and lists are an unsigned article concerning Foster Brothers’ craftsmen and their early use of machinery. Notes include material for a history of mirrors by Helen J. Foster, and "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster.
The majority of printed material relates to advertising and consists of catalogs and brochures about frames, mirrors, and published reproductions. Eight volumes of scrapbooks also contain printed material consisting of advertising, brochures and catalogs, form letters, and reproductions of miniatures and silhouettes published by Foster Brothers.
Family papers consist of a small number of personal papers of the founders, John Roy and Stephen Bartlett Foster, and also of Helen Foster Osborne (John’s daughter). They include Foster Oborne's 1973 reminiscence of having her portrait painted by William Paxton in 1923, John R. Foster’s personal account book and Foster Osborne’s correspondence with Ernest Donnelley concerning the sale of printing plates and dies from the miniature reproduction business.
Photographs are of founders John Roy and Stephen Bartlett Foster, some of their employees, and early pictures of the first Foster Brothers frame factory on Cambridge Street.
Names and Subject Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following terms:
Subjects-Topical:
Picture frame industry -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Picture frames and framing; Art -- Economic aspects
Types of Materials:
Photographs; Scrapbooks; Stencils; Drawings; Works of art
Names:
Osborne, Helen Foster; Foster, John R.; Foster, Stephen Bartlett; Osborne, S. W.; Richter, C. F.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 9 series:
Series 1: Correspondence, 1897-1942 (Box 1; 1.0 linear ft.)
Series 2: Stock Records, 1905-1942 (Boxes 2-6, 11, OVs 23-24, BVs 13-15; 6.2 linear ft.)
Series 3: Financial Records, 1892-1959 (Boxes 7-9; BVs 16-19; 3.3 linear ft.)
Series 4: Writings and Lists, 1920s-circa 1942 (Box 9; 0.25 linear ft.)
Series 5: Miscellaneous Business Records, 1898-1939 (Box 10; 7 folders)
Series 6: Printed Material, 1893-1947 (Box 10, OV 25; 0.25 linear ft.)
Series 7: Scrapbooks, 1906-1942 (Boxes 10, 12, BVs 20-22; 1.3 linear ft.)
Series 8: Family Papers, 1875-1973 (Box 10; 6 folders
Series 9: Photographs, circa 1880s-1918 (Box 10; 5 folders)
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Correspondence, 1897-1942, Series 1:; (Box 1; 1.0 linear ft.)
  Business correspondence with suppliers, distributors, and wholesale and retail customers concerns routine matters and special orders. The correspondence dated 1897-1941 is relatively sparse and primarily concerns copyright of artwork reproduced by Foster Brothers that was sold, framed, in gift shops, department and furniture stores.
  The year 1942, the company's last year in business, is well documented. Of particular interest are letters from S. W. Osborne (Margaret Foster’s husband) written while traveling to meet with wholesale clients in cities throughout the Northeast and Midwest.
  Chronological correspondence is followed by alphabetically arranged correspondence.
  - Correspondence, 1897-1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1921 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1922-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abbott – Austin-Hastings Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Babcock – Bittinger, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boaler Burchell and Dillon – Boyce Studio, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brandenburg – Butterfield, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cabot – Closson Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cocks – Cusik Studios, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Davenport – Drakenfeld Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - E and E Art Shop – Fulda, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gamble – Gump’s, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hagerty – Hurley, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ideal Furniture Co. – Jordan, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Kahn’s Art Gallery – Kromhaut, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lake – Lyon Furniture Mercantile Agency, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Macy and Co. – McVicker, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - M/E Framing Guild – Myers, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Nature Food Centres – Osborn, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Osborne, S. W., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ozark Arts and Crafts Center – Payne, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - P P and H Moulding Co. – Putnam, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Radas – Ryder, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sanders Co. – Sebatia Products, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Shaker Gift Center Inc. – Swartz, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Taber – Vixsboxse Art Galleries, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Wadsworth, Howland and Co. – Waverly Fabrics, Inc., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Webb – Wyman, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Yale Athletic Association – Yuenger Manufacturing Co., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Stock Records, 1905-1942, Series 2:; (Boxes 2-6, 11, OVs 23-24, BVs 13-15; 6.2 linear ft.)
  This series contains stock cards, inventory records, and price lists in addition to blueprints, drawings, and stencils and designs for wood carving.
  Stock cards (mostly 8" x 10" pieces of mat board) describe merchandise produced or sold by Foster Brothers, including frames for pictures and mirrors, candlesticks, glove boxes, moldings, painted glass and stands. Each card contains at least one image (drawing, photograph, or printed reproduction) of the item and its stock or style number, and sometimes notes dimensions and prices. Some loose images are interfiled with the cards.
  A large number of paper stencils that were used to transfer carving designs to frames survive, although many are fragile. Many stencils are annotated with the corresponding stock or style number; other designs for woodcarving are merely drawn on paper. In addition, there are extensive drawings of frames and moldings, loose and in bound volumes, including finished, colored drawings by master craftsman C. F. Richter.
  One volume titled "Cost on Mirrors" (1929) analyzes the amount of time needed to carve, gild, and polish frames, the cost of materials, and prices of frames #1001-1308.
  - Stock Cards (Box 2)
    - Frames #515-4599, undated, (19 folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-19)
    - Frames #4600-5099, undated, (18 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-18)
    - Frames #5100-6011; unnumbered, undated, (18 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-18)
    - Candlesticks #1-8, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Glove Boxes #6-9, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Light Bracket; Wall Candelabra #1-2, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Moldings #1w-186w; #1-172; #4533-4966, undated, (see also BV 13) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Painted Glass #1-62, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
    - Pier Mirrors (#P1-P17), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stands #1-40; unnumbered, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - Blueprints (Box 5)
    - Mirrors #1004-1167, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Catalog (includes blueprints and printed reproductions) – Mirrors #1053-1143, undated, (1 vol.) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Cost on Mirrors," 1929, (1 vol.) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Drawings (hand colored) by C. F. Richter, (see also BVs 14-15) (Box 5)
    - Cabinets, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Foster Brothers Mirrors in Room Settings (unsigned), undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Inventories (Box 5)
    - Vol. 1: 1933-1942 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 2: 1939-1941, (loose leaf notebook, disbound) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 3: undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Lists, 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Price Books, (loose leaf notebooks, disbound) (Box 5)
    - Vol. 1: Stands and Frames, 1919-1938 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Vol. 2: Frames, 1919-1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Vol. 3: Frames, 1923-1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Price Lists, 1929-1942, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, #100s-#6000s, unnumbered, undated, (34 folders; see also OVs 23-24, BV 13) (Box 6, Folder 1-34)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, unnumbered, undated, (8 folders; see also OVs 23-24, BV 13) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 1-8)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving, (#1000s-2000s, 4000s), undated (Box OV 23)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving (unnumbered), undated (Box OV 24)
  - Stencils and Designs for Woodcarving (unnumbered), 1905 (Box BV 13)
  - Drawings of Moldings, #1-3038, 1905 (Box BV 13)
  - Drawings (probably by C. F. Richter), "Sketches" (mirrors and frames), undated (Box BV 14)
  - Drawings (probably by C. F. Richter), "Mirrors and Frames," undated, (see also Box 5, BV 14; includes boxes, stands, letterhead design, printed reproductions; some loose items) (Box BV 15)
- Financial Records, 1892-1959, Series 3:; (Boxes 7-9; BVs 16-19; 3.3 linear ft.)
  Financial records consist mainly of accounting records, but also include annual financial reports, orders, and sales records. There are relatively few records before the early 1900s.
  - Accounting Records (Box 7)
    - Account Balances, Wholesale and Retail, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Accounts Payable, A-Z, 1936-1941, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - Accounts Payable, Summary, 1919-1938, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Accounts Receivable, A-Z, 1907-1940, (4 folders; 5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
    - Accounts Receivable, Summary, 1919-1938, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Advertising, 1928-1931, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Automobile, Reserve for Depreciation, 1931-1937, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Balance Sheets, 1919-1930 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Balances, Sundry Credit and Debit, 1931, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Bank Deposits, 1919-1939, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cash, 1919-1939, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 1: Jan. 11, 1938-Jan. 1, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 2: Jan. 3-Nov. 1, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 3: Nov. 13, 1939-Sept., 21, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 4: Sept. 23, 1940-Sept. 6, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 5: 1939, (see: BV 16) (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 6: 1940, (see: BV 17) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Cash Journal, Vol. 7: 1941, (see: BV 18) (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Code Numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Consignments, 1935-1941, (1 vol.) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Expenses, Factory and Store, 1900-1931, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Foster, Georgette K., Helen J., John R. and Estate of John R., 1902-1938, (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Furniture and Fixtures, 1919-1938, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - General Ledger, Profit and Loss, 1938, (see: BV 19) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Insurance, 1937-1938, (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Interest and Discount, 1919-1939, (5" x 8") (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Inventories, Consigned, Factory, and Store, 1919-1938, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Inventories, Factory and Store Equipment, Supplies, Fixtures, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Investment Account, 1919-1932, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Payroll, 1931, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 1: 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 2: 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Payroll - Factory, Vol. 3: 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Profit and Loss, 1919-1939, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Sales and Purchases, 1919-1938, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Sales and Purchases; Expenses, 1939-1942 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, 1925-1931, (5" x 8" cards) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Annual Financial Reports, 1925-1932 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Annual Financial Reports, 1934-1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Order Books – Retail, Vol. 1: 1939 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Order Books – Retail, Vol. 2: 1940 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Order Books – Retail, Vol. 3: 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Order Books – Wholesale, Vol. 1: 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Order Books – Wholesale, Vol. 2: 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sales, Vols. 1-3: 1892-1910 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sales, Vol. 4: 1937-1939, (wrapped package) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sales, Vol. 5: 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sales Records, Jan. 1942-Jan. 1943, (13 folders) (Box 9, Folder 2-14)
  - Sales, Monthly Summaries, 1926-1942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Sales, Davidson, C. E., 1938-1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sales, Wholesale Sales Trips (itineraries, customer lists, expenses, sales), 1930-1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 5, 1959 (Box BV 16)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 6, 1940 (Box BV 17)
  - Accounting Records, Cash Journal, Vol. 7, 1941 (Box BV 18)
  - Accounting Records, General Ledger, Profit and Loss, 1938 (Box BV 19)
- Writings and Lists, 1920s-circa 1942, Series 4:; (Box 9; 0.25 linear ft.)
  Writings consist of articles, lists and notes. An unsigned article concerns Foster Brothers’ craftsmen and their early use of machinery. Notes include material for a history of mirrors by Helen J. Foster, and "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster.
  - Articles by Unknown, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Draft of Mirror Brochure (with illustration), undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lists, Mailing, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Lists, Store and Factory Locations; Unusual items Framed for Customers by Helen Foster, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lists, Trade (by city), 1939 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lists, Retail Customers (Arlington, Belmont, Boston, Brookline, Cambridge, Lexington, Medfords, Worcester), undated, (8 vols. in 2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
  - Lists, Wholesale New England Customers or Possible Customers by Helen Foster, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Notebooks, Helen Foster – Business Information, A-Z, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Notebooks, John R. Foster – Notes and Figures; Lists, 1920s-1930s, (2 vols, disbound) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Notebooks, Margaret J. Melly [Mrs. McLaughlin] (in charge of wholesale orders and advertising) and Helen J. Foster – "Interesting Information of All Kinds," undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Notes, Artist Biographies by Unknown, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Notes, History of Mirrors by Helen J. Foster, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Notes, Miscellaneous and Lists by Helen J. Foster, circa 1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Notes, Picture Frames; "The Art of Framing" by John R. Foster, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Notes, Reproductions Published by Foster Brothers, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Business Records, 1898-1939, Series 5:; (Box 10; 7 folders)
  Included in this series are copyright and trademark information, a building permit, and records relating to an exhibition of etchings by Dorsey Potter Tyson held at Foster Brothers.
  - Building Permit for Arlington, Mass., Factory, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Census of Manufacturers, 1929-1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Contracts (Telephone and Electric Co.), 1898-1907 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Copyright Registration for Photograph, "Irene" and Print, "Your Picture of Today Will be the Keepsake of Tomorrow," 1898, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition of Etchings by Dorsey Potter Tyson, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Insurance, Workmen’s Compensation, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Trademark of Foster Brothers, 1899 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Printed Material, 1893-1947, Series 6:; (Box 10, OV 25; 0.25 linear ft.)
  The majority of printed material relates to advertising and consists of catalogs and brochures about frames, mirrors, and published reproductions. Unless otherwise noted, all items were produced by or are about Foster Brothers. Scrapbooks in Series 7 contain additional printed material.
  - Advertising, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Advertising (R. H. Macy and Co., featuring Foster Brothers’ mirrors, frames, and reproductions), undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Broadside, undated, (see: OV 25) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Brochures about Reproductions (not Foster Brothers), undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Brochures and Catalogs, 1890s-1930s, undated, (3 folders; see also OV 25) (Box 10, Folder 12-14)
  - Business Card of Helen Foster, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, About/Mentioning Foster Brothers, 1893-1947, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, About Picture Frames, 1934, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, Miscellaneous Subjects, 1893, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1893-1894 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Frame Labels, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Order Form for Reproductions, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlet about History of 2 Park Street, Boston (Houghton Mifflin Co.), 1923 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Reproductions of Silhouettes Published by Foster Brothers, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Broadside, undated (Box OV 25)
  - Brochures and Catalogs (Box OV 25)
- Scrapbooks, 1906-1942, Series 7:; (Boxes 10, 12, BV 20-22; 1.3 linear ft.)
  8 volumes of scrapbooks contain printed material including clippings, advertising material, brochures and catalogs, form letters, and reproductions of miniatures and silhouettes published by Foster Brothers.
  - Vol. 1: Advertising, 1906-1914 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 2: Advertising, 1915-1923, undated, (see BV 20) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 3: Advertising, 1934-1942, (see BV 21) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 4: Advertising in Magazines, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 5: Advertising in Magazines, 1924-1934, undated, (disbound volume; see Box 12) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 6: Advertising in Magazines, 1927-1931 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 7: Reproductions of Miniatures and Silhouettes (published by Foster Brothers), undated, (See: Box 12) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 8: Reproductions of Drawings by Alfred Shaw, Francis Getty, Kenneth Conant (copyrighted and published by Foster Brothers), 1921-1930, (see BV 22) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Loose Items [from unidentified scrapbook(s)], 1924-1932, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Vol. 5: Advertising in Magazines, 1924-1934, undated (Box 12 (sol))
  - Vol. 7: Reproductions of Miniatures and Silhouettes (published by Foster Brothers), undated (Box 12 (sol))
  - Vol. 2: Advertising, 1915-1923, undated (Box BV 20)
  - Vol. 3: Advertising, 1934-1942 (Box BV 21)
  - Vol. 8: Reproductions of Drawings by Alfred Shaw, Francis Getty, Kenneth Conant (copyrighted and published by Foster Brothers), 1921-1930 (Box BV 22)
- Family Papers, 1875-1973, Series 8:; (Box 10; 6 folders)